How do you fight for the care you and
your loved ones deserve listen to real
life stories of inclusion and winning
Against All Odds and how these
experiences change lives for the better
I'm Ann a champion for inclusivity and a
manual life policy owner since 2009 and
these are the stories of peach and Mark
what we are looking for as a couple is
for my son who has special needs
when we say we need coverage
for him the answer is always sorry
the special needs automatic rejection
that's my friend who recently
became a manual life Agent I said this is what
I need and I know it will be
difficult but let's do something um
like you I got rejected from
several insurance companies at first if
I May ask why why what is
it I am a hib positive the
preparation because
my medical examinations my laboratories are
difficult I lost hope I don't want to
take it because I can't be
accepted and then I found
the man life I looked for a friend who
has become my friend now so That's it
really No  I love
my child and I know he can't do
it so I want the same security the
same stability in their life know that
there is Hope Besides being happy with
myself I'm happy with my child I'm also
advocating for other parents find a
manual life agent that will advocate for
[Music]
you y